✔ edits use server revision; a delayed acknowledgement preserves and sends the current draft (6.1171ms)
✔ tab A revision five rejected after tab B six stays unsaved and never retries automatically (2.1481ms)
✔ equal-revision conflict allows explicit server choice without writing (3.1093ms)
✔ recovery uses acknowledged revision, not timestamp, and preserves legacy/conflicting drafts (3.9338ms)
✔ finalized or expired rejection retains recovery and never acknowledges the answer (1.3806ms)
✔ pending save flush waits for acknowledgement (1.625ms)
✔ an acknowledgement cannot remove a different draft written by another tab (1.5104ms)
ℹ tests 7
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 7
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 41.6254
